Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Video Productions, 1982-2018; 13.5 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 906 MiniDV; 470 U-matic; 93 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 81 Betacam_SP; 26 Betacam; 58 DVCAM; 27 VHS; 5 Hi8; 3 audiocassettes; 1.538 Terabytes in 6,117 files
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- Outreach, 2004 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- Newsstand Photographs, 2004; cuid39284 (Box 193, Folder 4, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_141)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "The Real Face of Occupation", October 14, 2004; cuid39400 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1759, Box 147, Minidv 312_0850, Box 158, Minidv 312_1590, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_137)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Standing with the Women of Iraq", October 14, 2004; cuid39399 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0849, Box 158, Minidv 312_1606, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_132)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "National Insecurities" Logo and Credits, August 4, 2004 (Box 149, Minidv 312_1066)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "National Insecurities", October 14, 2004; cuid39398 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1758, Box 146, Minidv 312_0848, Box 147, Minidv 312_0852, Box 157, Minidv 312_1583, Box 158, Minidv 312_1589, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_134)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "The Art of Resistance", October 14, 2004; cuid39397 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1757, Box 146, Minidv 312_0847, Box 157, Minidv 312_1585, Box 158, Minidv 312_1591, 312_1592, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_130)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "The Art of Resistance," Spanish Version, Circa 2004 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0859)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Dance of Death" Pre-Show, Circa 2004 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1231)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Dance of Death", October 14, 2004; cuid39396 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1754, Box 146, Minidv 312_0846, Box 158, Minidv 312_1587, 312_1603, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_136)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Dance of Death" Spanish Version, Circa 2004 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0858)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Erasing Memory: The Cultural Destruction of Iraq", October 14, 2004; cuid39395 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1749, 312_1755, Box 146, Minidv 312_0845, Box 158, Minidv 312_1602, 312_1604, 312_1605, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_133)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Globalization At Gunpoint", October 14, 2004; cuid39394 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1752, Box 146, Minidv 312_0844, Box 158, Minidv 312_1586, 312_1599, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_140)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "The World Says No to War", October 14, 2004; cuid39393 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1750, Box 146, Minidv 312_0843, Box 158, Minidv 312_1598, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_139)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Empire and Oil", October 14, 2004; cuid39392 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1753, Box 146, Minidv 312_0842, Box 157, Minidv 312_1582, Box 158, Minidv 312_1600, Box 160, Minidv 312_1730, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_138)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Baghdad", October 14, 2004; cuid39401 (Box 138, Vhs 312_1732, Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1756, Box 146, Minidv 312_0839, Box 147, Minidv 312_0851, Box 157, Minidv 312_1584, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_131)
    Film by Dario Bellini
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Channels of War", October 14, 2004; cuid39391 (Box 139, Betacam sp 312_1751, Box 146, Minidv 312_0841, Box 158, Minidv 312_1601, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_129)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- "Resistance At Home", October 14, 2004 (Box 146, Minidv 312_0840, Box 152, Minidv 312_1217)
    With Jeff Taylor and Asaf Zwali
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation, 2004; cuid39525 (Box 192, Dvd 312_1972, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_366)
  - Shocking and Awful: A Grassroots Response to War and Occupation -- Transcripts, 2007-2010; cuid39461 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_182)
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Photographs, 2004; cuid39441 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_142)
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Rania Masri Selects, January 19, 2004 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1281)
    Content includes Interview about planned war, military will stay there; American Government use nice words "finish the job, democracy," to make Americans agree to war; privatization of Iraqi economy
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Songool Chapak, January 29, 2004 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0882)
    Content includes Songool Chapak: "IGC Rep. Group interior at offices inside CPA"
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Women's Demonstration and Talk, January 30, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1124, 312_1127)
    Content includes Iraqi Women Demonstrate in Baghdad for greater representation in transitional government; informal panel discussion at Agadir Hotel with participants after demonstration; With Songool Chapak
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Hospital / Police, January-February, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1122)
    Content includes Al-Monsour Teaching Hospital Cancer Ward (Pediatric); Baghdad Police Station Interview with Iraqi Chief of Police (Group Interview)
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Anwar Jewad, January-February, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1123)
    Content includes Anwar Jewad Group Interview about 4 family members killed by US forces in random shooting; With Frances Anderson
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Squatters Compound and "Happy Families" Children's Circus, February 1, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1131)
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Christian Peacemakers Team and Shia Women's School, February 2, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1128, 312_1129)
    Content includes Christian Peacemakers Team group interview regarding detainees, Shia Women's School group interview with women living at Hawza in Khadimya, suburb of Baghdad
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Shia Women, February 2, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1138)
    Content includes Group Interview of Shia Women living at Hawza in Khadimya, suburb of Baghdad; CodePink Delegation
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Interview with Eman Khammous, Director of Occupation Watch Center, February 4, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1137, 312_1139, 312_1140, 312_1141, Box 151, Minidv 312_1181)
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Interview with Paola Gasparoli, Bridges 2 Baghdad, February 5, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1132, 312_1133, 312_1134)
    In this interview, Paola Gasparoli of Bridges 2 Baghdad discusses work with OWC on compensation claims for Iraqi random shooting victims.
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Radio in Baghdad, February 5, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1136)
    Content includes Channel Surfing in Baghdad. Freedom Radio (USA); Local Stations; International Stations
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Painting, circa February 6, 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1156)
  - CODEPINK in Iraq, February 28, 2004 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0883)
    Content includes police station, women's shelter
  - CODEPINK in Iraq -- Cheik Hayez Women's Clinic Interviews, Checkpoint at Medina Al Sadr, circa 2004 (Box 150, Minidv 312_1148)
  - Fayetteville Peace Protest, March 20, 2004 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1280)
  - Intrepid Freedom Protest, March 27, 2004 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1266)
    Content includes Long shot: Intrepid, NYC; Rock Concert with bad audio
  - Issam Shukri, Iraqi Labor Activist, March 30, 2004 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1257, Box 153, Minidv 312_1287)
  - Drawing the Assyrians, a poem by Elsa First, March, 2004 (Box 151, Minidv 312_1202)
    Produced by Jessica Glass, Freedom Fries Productions
  - David Gimbel, Archaeologist, April 6, 2004 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1275, 312_1276, 312_1283)
  - Occupation Watch, April, 2004 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1222, 312_1242)
  - Forbidden Pictures, May 15, 2004 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1285)
    With Larry Fink; Content includes Interview: photographer in documentary style; series "forbidden pictures," political tableau; large art prints, staged pictures of Bush groping women representing the world, etc.
  - Larry Everest Sound Bites, June 2, 2004 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1288)
    Content includes Interview, "Globalization at Gunpoint"; Control of world energy sources; Negotiations about war and oil with multinational corporations
  - "Good Vs Evil: Bush's Theology of War", June 18, 2004 (Box 151, Minidv 312_1200)
    With Free Speech TV, John Botucci
  - War Resisters League March, Chelsea, New York City, August 30-31, 2004 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1268, 312_1270, Box 153, Minidv 312_1272)
    With Brendan Schwartz; Shot by Veronica Davidov; Includes footage of mass arrests
  - Burhan Shakeer / Gimbel Interview, November 6, 2004 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1772, 312_1777, 312_1778)
    Content includes Gimbel and Glass Camera
  - Gebhard Selz Interview, November 7, 2004 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1779, 312_1782, 312_1783, 312_1785, 312_1786)
    Content includes Camera 2, Gimbel and Glass, Vienna
  - Franz Schuller, November 7, 2004 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1770, 312_1784, Box 161, Minidv 312_1787)
    Content includes Vienna
  - Gael Murphy's Humanitarian Mission, Jordan, December 2004 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1254, 312_1255)
  - "The Case of the Grinning Cat" by Chris Marker, Circa 2004 (Box 133, Vhs 312_0983)
  - "Imperial Geography" -- Production File, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Iraq: The Untold Story," A Film by Urban Hamid, 2004; cuid39510 (Box 148, Minidv 312_0934, Box 152, Minidv 312_1241, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_367)
  - Left Forum -- Mass Incarceration, Criminal Justice, Circa 2004 (Box 149, Minidv 312_1013)
  - Vienna, Circa 2004 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1774, 312_1781)
  - Mandate for Democracy with FAIR and League of Pissed Off Voters, December, 2004 - August, 2005 (Box 136, U-matic 312_1397, Box 138, Dvcam 312_1419, Box 151, Minidv 312_1171)
  - Iraq Source Footage and Photographs, 2004-2010; cuid39445 (Box 134, Dvcam 312_1049, 312_1050, 312_1053, Box 150, Minidv 312_1126, 312_1150, 312_1151, 312_1153, 312_1157, Box 151, Minidv 312_1161, 312_1169, 312_1178, 312_1180, 312_1186, Box 152, Minidv 312_1224, 312_1229, 312_1235, 312_1236, 312_1237, 312_1238, 312_1239, 312_1240, Box 154, Minidv 312_1364, 312_1365, 312_1366, 312_1367, 312_1368, 312_1369, 312_1370, 312_1371, 312_1372, 312_1373, 312_1374, 312_1375, 312_1376, 312_1377, 312_1378, Box 155, Minidv 312_1379, 312_1380, 312_1381, 312_1382, 312_1383, 312_1384, 312_1385, 312_1386, 312_1387, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_163)
    Includes several interviews, an art exhibit, and footage of the cities Baghdad, Fallujah, Basrah, and Kirkuk
  - Selections from "Unconventional TV", June 1, 2005 (Box 156, Minidv 312_1526)
    Produced by Jennifer Whitburn
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Production File, 2005-2009; cuid39285 (Box 76, Folder 25, Box 193, Folder 5, 6, 7, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_162)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq, circa June 2005; cuid39402 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1664, Box 160, Minidv 312_1702, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_368)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- The First 30 Minutes, Circa 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1655)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- 4 clips from the intro, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1729)
    Content includes Tony Alessandrini, Liz Roberts, Basak Ertur, Aysa Gubuku
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Camera 2, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1704, 312_1706, 312_1715, 312_1716, 312_1718)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Camera 3, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1700, 312_1723, 312_1725)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #1, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1727)
    Tape label notes "no sound"
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #2, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1708)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #3, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1728)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #4, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1726)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #5, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1712)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #6, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1724)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Mix #7, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1722)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Part One, Circa 2005 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0855)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Part Two, Circa 2005 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0856)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- "Saturday", circa 2004-2005; cuid39443 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_158)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- "Sunday", circa 2004-2005; cuid39444 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_160)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Istanbul, Day 1, June 24, 2005 (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1734, Box 139, Dvcam 312_1747, 312_1748, Box 158, Minidv 312_1607, 312_1608, 312_1609, 312_1610, 312_1611, 312_1612, 312_1613, 312_1614, 312_1615, 312_1616, 312_1617, Box 159, Minidv 312_1686)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Istanbul, Day 2, June 25, 2005 (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1736, 312_1737, 312_1738, 312_1739, 312_1740, 312_1741, Box 139, Dvcam 312_1745, 312_1746, Box 158, Minidv 312_1625, 312_1626, 312_1627, 312_1628, 312_1629, 312_1630, 312_1631, 312_1632, 312_1633, 312_1638)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Istanbul, Day 3, June 26, 2005 (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1735, Box 139, Dvcam 312_1744, Box 159, Minidv 312_1643, 312_1644)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- David's Interviews after Press Conference, June 27, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1689)
    Content includes Jurer, Participant, founder of radio
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Istanbul, Programs 1 and 2, August 3, 2005 (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1742)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- The Final Session, Circa 2005 (Box 90, Betacam sp 312_0124)
    First interview by Arundhati Roy
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- The Final Session, "Cost of War", Circa 2005 (Box 90, Betacam sp 312_0125)
    First interview by Eman Khanmanas
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Amy Bartholomew, June 24, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1620)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Arundhati Roy, Circa June, 2005; cuid39404 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1650, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_143)
    Contains opening remarks, closing remarks, and final press conference
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Ayse Gul Altinay, Circa June, 2005; cuid39406 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1658, 312_1697, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_144)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Barbara Olshansky, June 25, 2005; cuid39388 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1641, Box 159, Minidv 312_1646, 312_1659, 312_1691, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_145)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Biju Matthew, circa 2004-2005; cuid39442 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1667, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_146)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Christine Chinkin, Circa June, 2005; cuid39410 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1693, 312_1694, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_147)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Corinne Kumar, Circa June, 2005; cuid39411 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1663, 312_1696, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_148)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Dahr Jamail, June 25, 2005; cuid39390 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1649, Box 160, Minidv 312_1699, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_149)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- David Miller, June 24, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1621)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Denis Halliday, June 25, 2005; cuid39387 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1639, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_150)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Hans Von Sponeck, June 24, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1692)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Herbert Docena, Circa June, 2005; cuid39405 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1651, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_151)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Joel Kovel, June 25, 2005; cuid39389 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1642, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_152)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Joel Kovel and Thomas Fasy, June, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1653, 312_1656)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Johan Galtung, June 25, 2005; cuid39386 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1635, 312_1652, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_153)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Jury, Circa 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1710)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Khaled Fahmy, June 24, 2005; cuid39385 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1624, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_154)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Larry Everest, June 24, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1645)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Military Families, Circa June, 2005 (Box 160, Minidv 312_1709)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Nadje Al-Ali, Circa June, 2005; cuid39412 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1698, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_155)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- New York, Circa 2005 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0853, 312_0854, 312_0857)
    Produced by Alpa Patel
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Niloufer Bhagwat, Circa June, 2005; cuid39409 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1657, 312_1666, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_156)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Phil Shiner, June 24, 2005 (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1733, Box 158, Minidv 312_1623)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Professor Galtung, Nameen Al-Muffi, June 25, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1636, 312_1637)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Richard Falk, Circa June, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1648)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Samir Amin, Circa June, 2005; cuid39407 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1660, 312_1695, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_157)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Saul Landau, June 24, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1618)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Soaud Naji Al-Azzawi, Circa June, 2005; cuid39408 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1654, 312_1662, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_159)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Sunday Uplink, Circa June, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1647, 312_1681)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Thomas Fasy, June 25, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1634)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Tim Goodrich, Arundhati Roy, June 25, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1640, Box 159, Minidv 312_1661)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Tony Alessandrini, June 24, 2005 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1619)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq -- Walden Bello, June 24, 2005; cuid39384 (Box 158, Minidv 312_1622, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_161)
  - The World Tribunal on Iraq, September 8, 2005 (Box 159, Minidv 312_1665)
  - Anti-War Protest, Washington, DC -- Black Voices for Peace, September 21-23, 2005 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1799, 312_1801, 312_1807, 312_1812, 312_1813, 312_1814)
    With appearances by Emira Woods, Alih Booker, Brenda Stokely, Damu Smith, and Reverend Vivian
  - Anti-War Protest, Washington, DC -- Critical Mass, September 23, 2005 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1796)
  - Anti-War Protest, Washington, DC -- Bring the Troops Home, September 24, 2005 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1795, 312_1798, 312_1800, 312_1808, 312_1809, 312_1811)
    Produced by Jo Law Productions
  - Anti-War Protest, Washington, DC, September 24 - 26, 2005 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1791, 312_1792, 312_1793, 312_1802, 312_1803, 312_1804, 312_1806, 312_1810)
    Footage of the 300,000 person anti-war protest at the White House
  - Master Program Tapes, September 24, 2005 (Box 134, Dvcam 312_1051, 312_1052)
  - Link TV -- ID Spot, Logo Still Graphic, September 20, 2005 (Box 161, Minidv 312_1794)
  - Howard Zinn, October 13, 2005 (Box 148, Minidv 312_0938)
  - Interviews, New York City, October 27, 2005 (Box 153, Minidv 312_1277)
    Content includes interviews of people on the street in NYC; Quincy Gow, interviewer, Q and A, Q and E; camera: Sam Alcott
  - Ajamau Interview, November, 2005 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0863)
  - "Stop the War" Video Evidence in Support of Tony Benn's Submission to the UN and UK Attorney General, December, 2005; cuid39511 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_369)
  - CBS # 410, October 14 - November 1, 2005 (Box 138, Vhs 312_1465)
  - Demetra, Maurice, October 16, 2005 (Box 152, Minidv 312_1223)
  - NBC # 411, October 18 - 30, 2005 (Box 138, Vhs 312_1466)
  - ABC # 412, October 18 - 30, 2005 (Box 138, Vhs 312_1467)
  - Eric Learner's PBS FrontLine "On Torture", October 19, 2005 (Box 132, Vhs 312_0967, Box 148, Minidv 312_0935)
  - "Do You Know What it Means to Miss New Orleans?", 2005; cuid39446 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_164)
  - DVD Production Notes, circa 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Greensboro: An American City" -- Production File, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration, 2005-2006; cuid39527 (Box 148, Minidv 312_0990, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_373)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- "Opening Session", October 21, 2005 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1025)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- Day 1, October 21, 2005 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1028, 312_1029, Box 148, Minidv 312_0992, 312_0993, 312_0994, Box 149, Minidv 312_1000)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- Day 2, October 22, 2005 (Box 132, Dvcam 312_0973, Box 133, Dvcam 312_1026, 312_1027, Box 149, Minidv 312_1001, 312_1002, 312_1003)
    312_1026 includes "Morning Session," "Wars of Aggression," "Global Warming"; 312_1027 includes "Saturday Afternoon Katrina Testimony."
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- "Wars of Aggression," Hammerstein Ballroom, New York City, circa October, 2005; cuid39403 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1030, 312_1031, Box 148, Minidv 312_0995, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_376)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- "Global Warming, HIV, Katrina," Hammerstein Ballroom, New York City, circa October, 2005 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1032, 312_1033)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- "Destruction of the Global Environment", circa October, 2005 (Box 149, Minidv 312_0996, 312_0999)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- "Torture and Detention", circa October, 2005 (Box 149, Minidv 312_0997)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- "Katrina", circa October, 2005 (Box 149, Minidv 312_0998)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration -- Press Conference, DC, January 10, 2006 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1034)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration, January 20, 2006 (Box 133, Dvcam 312_1018, 312_1024, Box 148, Minidv 312_0927, Box 149, Minidv 312_1007, 312_1009)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration, January 20-21, 2006 (Box 148, Minidv 312_0959)
  - International Commission of Inquiry on Crimes Against Humanity of the Bush Administration, January 21, 2006 (Box 132, Dvcam 312_0970, Box 133, Dvcam 312_1019, 312_1020, 312_1021, Box 148, Minidv 312_0966)
    With Ted Gluck, Chris Joy, Josh Tolkien, Tom Goldtooth